  { "question": "بيت", "answer": "ب ي ت" },
  { "question": "رجل", "answer": "ر ج ل" },
  { "question": "امرأة", "answer": "ا م ر أ ة" },
  { "question": "ولد", "answer": "و ل د" },
  { "question": "فتاة", "answer": "ف ت ا ة" },
  { "question": "ماء", "answer": "م ا ء" },
  { "question": "نار", "answer": "ن ا ر" },
  { "question": "شمس", "answer": "ش م س" },
  { "question": "قمر", "answer": "ق م ر" },
  { "question": "ليل", "answer": "ل ي ل" },
  { "question": "نهار", "answer": "ن ه ا ر" },
  { "question": "جبل", "answer": "ج ب ل" },
  { "question": "سهل", "answer": "س ه ل" },
  { "question": "شجرة", "answer": "ش ج ر ة" },
  { "question": "زهرة", "answer": "ز ه ر ة" },
  { "question": "طير", "answer": "ط ي ر" },
  { "question": "أسد", "answer": "أ س د" },
  { "question": "ذئب", "answer": "ذ ئ ب" },
  { "question": "جمل", "answer": "ج م ل" },
  { "question": "بقر", "answer": "ب ق ر" },
  { "question": "غنم", "answer": "غ ن م" },
  { "question": "كتاب", "answer": "ك ت ا ب" },
  { "question": "قلم", "answer": "ق ل م" },
  { "question": "ورقة", "answer": "و ر ق ة" },
  { "question": "منزل", "answer": "م ن ز ل" },
  { "question": "مدرسة", "answer": "م د ر س ة" },
  { "question": "مستشفى", "answer": "م س ت ش ف ى" },
  { "question": "متجر", "answer": "م ت ج ر" },
  { "question": "مطعم", "answer": "م ط ع م" },
  { "question": "سيارة", "answer": "س ي أ ر ة" },
  { "question": "دراجة", "answer": "د ر ا ج ة" },
  { "question": "طائرة", "answer": "ط ا ئ ر ة" },
  { "question": "قطار", "answer": "ق ط ا ر" },
  { "question": "سفينة", "answer": "س ف ي ن ة" },